hendrix.edu 2015-04-29

# Hendrix College | Privacy Policy

0 out of 50 found this helpful. 

The following discloses information gathering and dissemination practices for the Hendrix College website:

## Our Commitment to Privacy

Hendrix College strives to ensure the privacy and accuracy of your confidential information. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## Information Gathering

Non-identifying site activity data is collected throughout the Hendrix web site and includes information on domains, browsers, operating systems, IP addresses, and pages accessed.

On some pages, you can make a donation, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Email address 
  * Phone number 
  * Credit/Debit Card Information 
  * (etc.)  

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you make a gift online in honor or in memory of a friend or loved one and would like the college to send acknowledgement to the recipient or a designate, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:

  * Name 
  * Address 
  * Phone Number 
  * (etc.) 

## Use of Information

We do not actively share personal information gathered from our Web servers. We do not provide or sell any personally identifiable information to outside agencies (third parties).

We use the information you provide about yourself for Hendrix Advancement records only. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to process a donation or other such actions. If you mark an information field "public" this means that only registered users of the net community will be able to access your information. This is how the college keeps your information safe. Your information will never be on the public domain of the Hendrix website.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive information about the College. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the appropriate registration form.

Finally, we use non-identifying and aggregate site-activity for standard reporting and analysis to improve site content, usability, and functionality.

## Security

We make every effort to protect the personal information of those in the Hendrix community, including those who visit Hendrix web sites. The College has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information.

## Links to Off-Site Content

The Hendrix web site contains links to a number of external Web sites. The College is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the external Web sites to which we link.

## How You Can Correct Your Information

_General Information:_

Contact the Hendrix Office of Communications at (501) 450-1462 or by email at [news@hendrix.edu](mailto:news@hendrix.edu). Additionally you may contact the webmaster at [webmaster@hendrix.edu](mailto:webmaster@hendrix.edu). 

_Alumni Information:_

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by using the "My Profile" options under "My Account" in the Hendrix Web Community menu. If you should have any problems with this process, contact the Hendrix Advancement office at (501) 450-1223 or by email at [alumni@hendrix.edu](mailto:alumni@hendrix.edu). 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 501-450-1462 or send us an email at [webmaster@hendrix.edu](mailto:webmaster@hendrix.edu).

Did you find this helpful? Yes No
